

Rafi Rajoyan

(818) 877 64351 | rafirjr@gmail.com | 2645 Sleepy Hollow Pl, Glendale CA 91206

PROFILE

4

For the past 4 years, I have dedicated myself to learn and utilize as much programming skills as possible in order to ultimately obtain my Computer Science degree. I try to seek and grasp every opportunity that comes my way because at the end of the day my growth as a student and as a person is the most important to me.

MY SKILLS

+

Diligent POS Systems

Python Calculus

Bootstrap Analytical

Conflict Resolution Adaptable

HTML/CSS Javascript

C++ Team-Building

Visual Studio/ VS Code 60 WPM - Typing

LANGUAGES

+

English - Native Proficiency

Armenian - Biliteracy Certified

REFERENCE



Greg Alaverdian Advanced Computer Care + 1 (818) 631-5580

WORK EXPERIENCES



Intern

(Sept. 2019 - Nov. 2019)

Information Technology Assistant

(Nov. 2019 - March 2020)

Advanced Computer Care - Glendale, CA

- Worked on setting up computers and networks for other client companies
- Replaced computer hardware with new and higher rated technology
- Answered customer questions related to IT issues and network problems

Business Department Web Developer

(Sept. 2020 - Dec 2020)

Glendale Community College - Glendale, CA

- Used HTML and Javascript to update existing features on the Business Department website
- Created new sub-links for student led organizations within the Business Department
- Worked with Business Department Chair to form new features on the website

Volunteer

(Nov. 2015 - Current)

Armenia Fund - Glendale, CA

- Answered phone inquiries related to customer donations for charity
- Inputted payment information into the computer system

EDUCATION



Associates for Transfer: Computer Science (2018 - Current)

Glendale Community College (GCC)

Clubs: Business Club Treasurer STEM Club President

GPA: 4.0 Awards:

Dean's Honors

High School Diploma (2015 - 2019)

Clark Magnet High School (CMHS)

Clubs: Armenian Club Treasurer

GPA: 4.3 SAT: 1400

Awards:

4.0 GPA Award CSF Award

4x Perfect Attendence